Sujay Mahadik



mahadik203@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/sujay-mahadik



+91 90041 33463



https://www.sujaymahadik.website/

Summary

I am often found juggling with interests that include coding, graphic design, all the way to appreciating good coffee and nerding out over pop fiction, astrophysics and dystopian literature. I have 4 years of experience in full stack front end development based around ReactJS and bootstrap, illustrations, graphics and motion design.

Working with Barclays around Enterprise and Data Integration Infrastruture Administration ETL tools include Informatica and Ab Initio

On the side I work with a remote, non-conforming design collective based in Paris focused on creating visual identity. Our collective has experience in diverse fields such as design, photography, animation among a few.

Experience



Co-Founder and Designer

The Jellyfish Collective

Jun 2020 - Present (6 months +)

Co-Founded a remote, non-conforming design collective based in Paris focused on creating visual identity. Our collective has experience in diverse fields such as design, photography, UI/UX design among a few.



Graduate Analyst

Barclays

Aug 2019 - Present (1 year 4 months +)

Working around Enterprise and Data Integration Infrastruture Administration

ETL tools:

- Informatica
- Ab Initio

Designed a Team Service First Dashboard for summarization of daily Incidents and Changes

Graphic Designer

Infin8y Labs

Sep 2016 - May 2020 (3 years 9 months)

Hobby Venture Co-Created with a college mate revolving around Graphic Design and Merchandise Production

Graphic Design and Motion Design

https://www.behance.net/sujay-mahadik

Experience with Adobe Design Suite - Adobe Illustration, Adobe After Effects

Undertook Freelance Web Development and Graphic Design Projects

- Built Portfolio Website: https://www.piyushbhisekar.com
- Hands on with UI kits and iframe integration for Spotify/Apple Music

Web Dev and Graphic Design https://www.thejellyfishcollective.co/

Project Intern

Persistent Systems

Sep 2017 - Jun 2018 (10 months)

The aim of the project was to create an Autonomous Drone and was done in a group of 6 students.

• Simulation and designing terrains in Unity 3D Game Engine

Design and Technical Head

MIT CREON

Aug 2016 - Feb 2018 (1 year 7 months)

Web-Dev of MIT CREON 17, MIT CREON 18 https://github.com/sujay-mahadik/c2018

- HTML, CSS
- SMTP and PDF generation for ticketing module
- Adobe Illustrator

Education

Fergusson College

Master of Arts - MA, Economics 2019 - 2021

Savitribai Phule Pune University

Bachelor of Engineering (BE) , Information Technology 2015 - 2019

Top 3% in Department

BE Project - Secure Document Transfer On Decentralized Web https://github.com/sujay-mahadik/secure-document-transfer Aug 2018 – Mar 2019

Project descriptionTechnologies Used

- IPFS
- ReactJS
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Smart Contracts

TE Course Work - Automated Student ERP https://github.com/sujay-mahadik/student-erp-by-ssa

Jun 2017 - Dec 2017

Includes customized time-table creation, attendance marker, adaptive testing of students as part of internal examinations, analysis based on the results of test.

The project involved working with:

- Database Management SQL
- PHP Scripting
- SMTP Mail Server Management
- Front End HTML, CSS and JS
- Pace Junior Science College

HSC, Science

2013 - 2015

Among Top 1%, Awarded research scholarship

National English School, ICSE

ICSE

Licenses & Certifications

AWS Fundamentals: Going Cloud-Native - Coursera EDSRWJK4FWTX

Blockchain Basics by University of Buffalo & The State University of New York -

Coursera

T682MSQWQARE

Smart Contracts by University at Buffalo & The State University of New York Coursera
GXN2XRK95XUT

- Internet Connection Cisco Networking Academy
 LTKPEEDADCK4
- Network Protocols and Architecture Cisco Networking Academy
 8ALZDM48SYWG
- The Data Scientist's Toolbox by Johns Hopkins University Coursera
 TPW5HGAGFFE9
- Textual Elements of Design: Fonts, Typography, and Spacing by University of Colorado Boulder Coursera

76XEHZZWN3GY

Print and Digital Elements of Design: Branding and User Experience by University of Colorado Boulder - Coursera

YP9CNVY3NPF9

Introduction to Philosophy by The University of Edinburgh - Coursera
M6SQT8L2KABN

Skills

HTML • React.js • Adobe Illustrator • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Bootstrap • Web Design • Adobe XD • Adobe InDesign • Adobe After Effects • User Interface Design

Honors & Awards

- Scholarship for Higher Education, Top 1% in Boards Maharashtra State Board of Secondary and Higher Education Society

 Mar 2015
- Primary School Scholarship
- International Olympiad of Mathematics 2008